[{"answer": "A huge siren.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "What was the first that you heard that made you realize there was a big event happening right outside?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "they're absolutely could be, I mean there are always, there's always second guessing in situations like this, but I believe given the route that she took from to very important places of power with very -- with a lot of security and law enforcement protecting people and particularly after what happened in 9/11 and the scare even most recently at the Navy Yard, I think everybody was, I know everybody was on high alert.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "What are you hearing about that?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well Piers, when we're walking outside which usually when I leave that Thursday lunch, we -- I usually walk underground, this just happened to be outside but the first thought that I had, the initial thought when I heard all the sirens and the law enforcement, I thought it was a dignitary being escorted then as I got closer to that corner, I knew there was more urgency to it and then I heard about three or four pops of gunfire, of course then, we knew it was very serious.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "When did you realize what had happened and what was your first fear?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "The weird caucus.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "What else did I call them?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "I'm not going to give up on the anarchist.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "So I mean do you think -- are you pledging to tone down the rhetoric a little bit and maybe that could help?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "You know, the Speaker and his leaders aren't talking about ObamaCare and getting rid of ObamaCare as far as negotiating is going in public.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Are the Republicans now if they -- well if we can keep it going 'till then we can do some kind of grand recovery plan which can get us off the wrap here?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I think right now, there are two basic facts I think that are operative here.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "How do you feel as a Democratic Senator, do you feel powerless at the moment?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well, I couldn't tell you where it is in the Senate side of things.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Is it Speaker Boehner or Ted Cruz?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well, my greatest fear is getting further and further into debt and not being able to climb out and also not being able to pay the bills, put food on the table, pay for the medications my daughter needs.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What is your biggest fear going forward?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "It's going to be difficult to handle.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Does that help you that knowledge or if this goes on for few weeks, does the pain you suffer in that short- term period just be really very difficult to handle?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "I think they're behaving like a bunch of spoiled children, like a bunch of five-year-olds throwing temper tantrums especially the Republicans.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What do you think Mr. Penders of the way the politicians are behaving over this in Washington?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "You're not happy what you're hearing, why?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "So President Obama didn't carry most congressional districts.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "And what is the combined impact?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Yeah, well I mean that's fine as an explanation for why we have a Republican House and a Democratic President but it's an excuse for why republicans have decided that they're going to hold hostage the normal operation of government in order to have negotiations.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "But what is your impression of the impact that's having right now?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Well, I have to say this is a scary situation for me.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "What is your concern about what is going on right now?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "I think especially for young Americans this is an amazing opportunity to make sure that we can treat you right, I mean the liaison (ph) therapy that happened because people don't have insurance it leads to morbidity and mortality and it's not right.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "You are a senior oncologist, you are at the sharp end of all this, what is your view?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "As of tomorrow actually the Head Start Program in Florida will be shutdown.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Tell me what you are going through right now, what your particular concern is?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "So, Star, you see, when you hear this it just makes me so bloody angry, right?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "ONES: In America.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Because you're like how can you allow this to happen in America?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Well, I think, I think -- I don't ...", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Michael you're shaking your head?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well, I think objectively we use of the terms bickering and squabbling and I think both sides are taking principal position ...", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "What is the practical reality and how we get out of this particular situation?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "ARONE: Yes, that was not ...", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "When you hear Harry Reid call them anarchists?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "...t he House...", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "You think?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Well, I think the Republicans made a miscalculation by raising the issue of defunding ObamaCare, it polled poorly voters truly didn't want it, delay ObamaCare polls better I think that probably would have been a foolish thing for them to go on a ...", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "You shutdown a government because you want to change parts of an established law?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "I think it's miscalculation by people who are principal politicians and I think ...", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Do you think what's going on to good principle politics?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Yeah, we're not the first to call and it's the question I'll tell you what I'll tell him.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "If President Rouhani pick the telephone up and called you, would you take that call?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "ETANYAHU: No, I wouldn't.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "And would you hesitate to take military action?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Yes, they'll work it out.", "docId": "131003pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "... damage the global economy?", "qSentId": 508}]